<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<Records>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>1</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Adams</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Dr. Michael F.</First_Name>
        <Title>Senior Merchant, New Busines</Title>
        <Institution>University of Georgia</Institution>
        <Bio>Dr. Michael F. Adams was named the 21st president of the University of Georgia on June 11, 1997. Under his leadership, the University of Georgia has attained its highest rankings ever and has grown from some 29,000 students to almost 35,000 students today. Now in his 16th year as President of the University of Georgia, he is one of America’s longest serving and best known university presidents.  Dry Adams holds a Ph.D. from The Ohio State University and has been awarded five honorary degrees. In May, Dr. Adams announced his intention to step down from the presidency effective June 30, 2013, saying, “I was privileged in 1997 to be given the opportunity to come to a university that had been very well served by its previous presidents, especially those in the modern era, Fred Davison, Henry King Stanford and Charles Knapp. I believe that my work here has continued the upward trajectory they established and that the next president will find a university positioned for extraordinary success.”</Bio>
		<URL>@ugactl</URL>
        <Sessions>0</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>2</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Alford</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Michael</First_Name>
        <Title>Senior Merchant, New Busines</Title>
        <Institution>University of Oklahoma</Institution>
        <Bio>Michael Alford joined The University of Oklahoma in November 2012 as Senior Associate Athletics Director for Development. He comes to Oklahoma from the NFL’s Dallas Cowboys where he served as Senior Director of Corporate Partnerships and Sales since 2008.  During his tenure with the Cowboys, Alford cultivated corporate relationships that resulted in hundreds of millions of dollars in contractual revenue for the club. He managed all aspects of programming for Cowboys Stadium, a state-of-the-art facility that opened in 2009, and has hosted numerous college football contests, concerts and other marquee events, including Super Bowl XLV. Alford oversaw the management and day-to-day operations for the marketing and sales department for the Dallas Cowboys and the Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders. In addition, he managed inventory and new business development for the Cowboys’ television and broadcast assets, and was also responsible for oversight of all facets of sponsorships, publications and internet, as well as the broadcast and telecast media departments for the Cowboys.</Bio>
		<URL>@MichaelAlfordOU</URL>
        <Sessions>1</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>3</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Allee</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Jennifer</First_Name>
        <Title>Senior Merchant, New Businesss</Title>
        <Institution>The University of Kansas</Institution>
        <Bio>Jennifer Allee started with The University of Kansas Athletics in January 2004 and serves as an Assistant Athletic Director for Marketing and Fan experience. Her main responsibility is promoting and implementing positive game-day fan experience for all Kansas sports. Before coming Kansas, Allee was a game-day assistant for the Kansas City Chiefs. While at The University of Kansas, she has spent time as the marketing coordinator, marketing manager and the assistant director of marketing. Allee was born in Kansas City, Mo. and attended Blue Valley High School in Stilwell, Kansas. In high school she played basketball and softball. She graduated from The University of Kansas in 2003 and received her master’s degree here in 2005. Allee is a member of the National Association of Collegiate Marketing Administrators and National Association of Collegiate Woman Athletics Administrators.</Bio>
		<URL>@KUAthletics</URL>
        <Sessions>2</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>4</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Anthis</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Jody</First_Name>
        <Title>Trademark Management &amp; Licensing</Title>
        <Institution>JPatton</Institution>
        <Bio>Jody Anthis currently serves as vice president of Licensing for JPatton. Jody has been with JPatton for 14 years and is the company’s longest tenured employee. Jody has been instrumental in the launch and management of the Logos On Demand, Stitches On Demand, and Holographics On Demand services for JPatton and The Collegiate Licensing Company.
            
Jody is a graduate of Kennesaw State University with a Bachelors of Science Degree in Sports Management.In 2006, Jody was ESPN’s #1 ranked player in ESPN Fantasy Baseball for NL only leagues. He is married with two daughters, ages 16 and 10.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
		<Sessions>3</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>5</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Baughman</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Dutch</First_Name>
        <Title>Founder, Chairman, and CEO</Title>
        <Institution>1A Athletics Directors Association</Institution>
        <Bio>Dutch Baughman serves as the Executive Director of the Division 1A Athletics Association. In addition to his responsibilities of administering the association, he works to bring focus on student athlete development and programs to 1A sports programs. He also serves as Founder and Director of the Athletics Director Institute, which provides an intense educational experience for associate directors of athletics who have aspirations of becoming an athletic director. Baughman has 38 years of experience in intercollegiate athletics. He began as a football coach at Ohio State, served as Senior Associate Director of Athletics at Northwestern, and Director of Athletics at Furman University, Virginia Tech, and Oregon State. Baughman also served as the Senior Executive Commissioner of the Southwest Conference from 1982 to 1987. In addition to his work in intercollegiate athletics, Baughman served in the United State Marine Corps and was an account executive with Merrill Lynch. Pierce, Fenner and Smith.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
		<Sessions>4</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>6</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Bauman</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Craig</First_Name>
        <Title>Founder, Chairman, and CEO</Title>
        <Institution>Oklahoma State University</Institution>
        <Bio>Craig Bauman oversees all athletic ticketing operations as Oklahoma State’s Assistant Athletic Director/Ticket Manager.  He began his career at Oklahoma State University as the Coordinator of Counter Sales/Student Tickets and was promoted in 2006 to Assistant Ticket Manager.  In 2009, he was promoted to Associate Ticket Manager with duties that included oversight of all ticketing operations for football as well as system administration for Oklahoma State University’s TicketMaster Ticketing System. Prior to working at Oklahoma State University, he worked at the University of Maryland Athletic Department as a Ticket Assistant and as an intern in the University of Pittsburgh ticket office. Bauman received a Bachelor’s degree in Sports Management from Robert Morris University. The New Castle, Pennsylvania native lives in Stillwater with his
wife Becky.
</Bio>
        <URL>@CraigBauman</URL>
		<Sessions>5</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>7</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Bernstein</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Bonnie</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Marketing and Brand Management</Title>
        <Institution>Campus Insiders</Institution>
        <Bio>Bonnie Bernstein is recognized by the American Sportscasters Association as one of the most accomplished female journalists in her field. After spending 17 years covering some of the nation’s most prestigious sports events on-air for ESPN and CBS, she is now helping build a network both in front of and behind the camera. Bernstein is the “face” and Vice President, Content and Brand Development, of Campus Insiders, a digital collaboration between IMG College, America’s premier college sports marketing company, and Silver Chalice Ventures. Bernstein graduated Magna Cum Laude from the University of Maryland’s prestigious Merrill College of Journalism. She currently serves on the College’s Board of Visitors as well as the Advisory Board for the Shirley Povich Center for Sports Journalism. While at College Park, Bernstein was a four-time Academic All-America selection (gymnastics) and received the Thomas M. Fields Award for academic and athletic excellence.</Bio>
		<URL>@BonnieBernstein</URL>
        <Sessions>6</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>8</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Bozich</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Joe</First_Name>
        <Title>Licensing &amp; Marketing Director, Auxiliary Services</Title>
        <Institution>Knights Apparel</Institution>
        <Bio>Joe Bozich is founder, chairman of the board, and CEO of Knights Apparel, one of the largest producers of college apparel. Bozich is also the creator of the Alta Gracia brand, collegiate licensed apparel produced in the Dominican Republican in a factory paying a living wage. Bozich has extensive manufacturing, sourcing, marketing, and operations experience. He began his career as vice president of sales and marketing with Gold’s Gym and quickly advanced to the position of president of the clothing division. A graduate of Vanderbilt University with a B.S. in Mathematics, Bozich was the 1985 NCAA National Bodybuilding champion and served as a spokesperson for Weider Enterprises, Gold’s Gym, the IFBB, and Mattel Corporation. He was named Ernst &amp; Young’s 2005 Entrepreneur of the Year for the Illinois Region. Huffington Post named Bozich its “Ultimate Game Changer in Style” for 2010 for his Alta Gracia program.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
		<Sessions>7</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>9</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Brandt</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Eric</First_Name>
        <Title>Trademark Licensing Coordinator</Title>
        <Institution>The University of Oregon</Institution>
        <Bio>Eric Brandt is the Director of Food and Hospitality at the University of Oregon where he earned his marketing degree from the Lundquist School of business in 1982. Brandt is responsible for retail concessions, corporate hospitality, chair back leases and rentals, program sales, and luxury suite catering.
            
In addition, Brandt produces a football game tailgate party held inside the Moshofsky Indoor Practice Facility featuring live music, rally and dance team performances, interactive games, sit-down dining for 6,000, live radio broadcasts, and a “March to Victory” appearance by the football team.
            
Brandt has long enjoyed opportunities afforded those living in the American West including time spent treed by a Grizzly bear, near drowning at the bottom of the Grand Canyon, and marginally controlled downhill runs on local ski slopes.
</Bio>
		<URL></URL>
        <Sessions>8</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>10</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Byers</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Sharon</First_Name>
        <Title>Trademark Licensing Coordinator</Title>
        <Institution>Coca-Cola North America</Institution>
        <Bio>Sharon Byers graduated from Auburn University in 1987 with a BS in Finance and went on to receive an additional degree in Accounting from Georgia State University. Byers’s current position, Senior Vice President of Sports and Entertainment Marketing for the Coca-Cola North American Business Unit, includes the development of national marketing programs across the portfolio of brands for the Coca-Cola’s premier partnerships with American Idol, NASCAR, NCAA, Olympics, top colleges and universities, ESPN College Gameday, and many others. Additionally, her work includes development of Coca-Cola’s sports and entertainment marketing strategies, league, and talent relationship management including LeBron James, Jennifer Anniston, Kobe Bryant, Carrie Underwood and other key partnerships.  In 2012, Byers was named one of Sports Business Journal’s “Game Changers” as well as named one of the “50 Most Powerful People in Sports.”</Bio>
		<URL></URL>
        <Sessions>9</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
	<Record>
        <Speaker_Number>11</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Carr</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Scott</First_Name>
        <Title>Licensing &amp; Marketing Director, Auxiliary Services</Title>
        <Institution>Auburn University</Institution>
        <Bio>Carr oversees the external affairs of the Athletics Department. He has direct supervision of the Marketing and Promotions department, Media Relations, Ticket Office, Tigers Unlimited Annual Fund, and Community Relations.  He is responsible for the game day experience at all sporting events and oversees all Athletics Department contracts, including but not limited to IMG, Under Armour, and Sodexho (concessions). Prior to his employment with Auburn, he served at Southern Miss in the following positions: Deputy Director of Athletics, External Affairs (2006-2009); Associate Director of Athletics, External Affairs (2003-06); Assistant Director of Athletics for External Affairs (2002); Assistant Director of Athletics, Facilities and Event Management (2001-2002). The most recent position he held was the Deputy Director of Athletics, External Affairs (2006-2009).  Prior to Southern Miss, Carr worked in various capacities with the FedEx Orange Bowl in Miami, FL (1997-2001).</Bio>
        <URL>@AUAthletics</URL>
		<Sessions>10</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>12</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Carstens</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Matt</First_Name>
        <Title>Executive Director</Title>
        <Institution>ACC Digital Network/Silver Chalice</Institution>
        <Bio>Prior to joining Silver Chalice, Matt Carstens spent over ten years developing expertise in television and digital video production, programming and advertising sales.  From 1999-2004, he held programming and production positions at ESPN, gaining experience in both studio and remote production and advancing while learning from many of the best in the sports media industry.  Carstens was key in creating, operating and growing the digital media division at Intersport, Inc.
            
Carstens helped create and launch entertainment news, music, Spanish-language programming, and sports networks for digital platforms.  In addition to both mobile and broadband production and programming, he also played heavy roles in marketing and advertising sales and implementation, oversaw the building of two digital studios, and created and supervised production and programming teams to support the networks. Carstens is also responsible for the creation of video properties for digital brands such as Facebook, SportsIllustrated.com, Chase, Sprint and LifeLock.
</Bio>
		<URL>@theACCDN</URL>
        <Sessions>11</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>13</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Chase</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Randy</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Licensing</Title>
        <Institution>EA Sports</Institution>
        <Bio>Randy Chase serves as director of EA Sports. He joined EA over six years ago and has led the marketing efforts for several EA SPORTS franchises including Madden, Tiger Woods PGA Tour, NASCAR, and EA Sports MMA. Chase has been working on the NCAA Football franchise for three years and has championed efforts such as the NCAA Football Cover Vote, ESPN - Traditions Vote, and NCAA Football 14 Ultimate Team. He also values the importance of having an ongoing conversation with the consumer, which has led to the NCAA Football Facebook page acquiring over 1.6M passionate college football fans. Prior to EA SPORTS, Randy worked at Hard Rock Café International, Universal Orlando, and Walt Disney World Marketing.</Bio>
		<URL>@randychase75</URL>
        <Sessions>12</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>14</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>D Angelo</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Steven</First_Name>
        <Title>Assistant Vice President of Business Development</Title>
        <Institution>'47 Brand</Institution>
        <Bio>Steven D’Angelo is the owner and vice president of ‘47 Brand and has led the company in many different capacities over the past 20 years. He also oversaw Twins Worldwide, a successful overseas extension of Twins’ sports-licensed product. He brings a vast knowledge base to the licensed business. Since his graduation from UMass Amherst, he has been involved in virtually every facet of the licensing industry.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
		<Sessions>13</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>15</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Dunlap</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Carson</First_Name>
        <Title>Owner</Title>
        <Institution>Oregon State University</Institution>
        <Bio>Carson Dunlap is a creative marketing professional with a passion for sports. As manager of Trademark Licensing at Oregon State, Carson works to protect, enhance, and elevate the University’s brand image and visibility. Overseeing the day-to-day activities of the program, Carson manages relationships with over 400 licensees and retailers. Since starting in 2009, royalty revenue has increased by more than 30 percent, and retail distribution of Oregon State product has significantly grown. Carson graduated from Oregon State with a B.S. in Business Administration, with areas of focus in marketing, international business, and athletic administration. Currently, he is a MBA candidate and expected to complete the program in 2014.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
		<Sessions>14</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>16</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Ferris</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Christopher</First_Name>
        <Title>Owner</Title>
        <Institution>The University of Pittsburgh</Institution>
        <Bio>Chris Ferris, Associate Athletic Director, External Relations is in his 14th year in the Pittsburgh Athletic Department. A native of Upper St. Clair, Pa., Ferris joined the Pittsburgh Athletic Department in 1994 when he served as a student equipment manager. The following year, he worked as an undergraduate intern with the Media Relations and Marketing departments. Ferris is a 1998 graduate of Pittsburgh with a bachelor’s degree in Business and Communications. He also earned his master’s degree at the University of Pittsburgh’s Katz Graduate School of Business.</Bio>
        <URL>@PittAthletics</URL>
		<Sessions>15</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>17</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Foley</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Brian</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Official Rings</Title>
        <Institution>Mass Relevance</Institution>
        <Bio>Brian Foley is the Director of Global Sports for Mass Relevance, a social curation and display platform that enables teams, leagues, media and brands to engage their fans by visualizing real-time social content from all major networks on any digital end-point. The Mass Relevance’s sports client roster includes the Olympics, MLB, NBA, NFL, NASCAR, and countless teams and leagues from around the world.  Prior to joining Mass Relevance, Foley worked as the Director of Business Development for Position Sports, a national sports marketing firm that specializes in corporate branding, media relations, marketing, consulting and event operations. During that time, he developed initiatives with clients including Nike, Jordan Brand, and USA Basketball, and sold sponsorships for numerous events both domestic and international. Originally from Boston, Foley is a proud alumnus of Syracuse University.</Bio>
        <URL>@massrelevance</URL>
		<Sessions>16</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
    <Speaker_Number>18</Speaker_Number>
    <Last_Name>Greer</Last_Name>
    <First_Name>Ken</First_Name>
    <Title>Owner</Title>
    <Institution>Augeo + Greer</Institution>
    <Bio>Since founding his agency in the early ‘80’s, and now leading the marketing charge at Augeo, Ken Greer’s one-of-a-kind combination of creative and strategic marketing skills has been the driving force behind the transformation of both consumer and business-to-business enterprises. His thinking was featured in the business best seller, The World is Flat, and he has been cited in the New York Times for his fresh approach to the convergence of technology and communications. Greer helps clients take full advantage of the ever-evolving media convergence – social, video, interactive, mobile and whatever might be coming next. He’s a brand futurist, and his unique “Luminary Process” recently helped Microsoft Bing and Mayo Health Clinic with their employer branding efforts. In addition to his duties as Chief Marketing Officer at Augeo, Greer is the President and fearless leader of Augeo+Greer, a Brand Strategy and Communications Design Agency.</Bio>
        <URL>@AugeoGreer</URL>
		<Sessions>17</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>19</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Hinckley</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Shane</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Trademarks and Licensing</Title>
        <Institution>Texas A&amp;M University</Institution>
        <Bio>Shane Hinckley is currently serving as interim vice president of Marketing and Communications at Texas A&amp;M University, where he oversees a variety of University functions and services. In addition to this role, Hinckley is responsible for the supervision of new and existing business opportunities with the University. He also oversees the on-campus bookstore and the state license plate program, as well as other business and marketing opportunities.
            
He also directs the Texas A&amp;M licensing program, which administers the use of the University’s name, marks, and still and moving images with internal and external partners. Prior to his joining Texas A&amp;M, Hinckley worked as the director of marketing &amp; licensing for auxiliary services at the University of Utah. He also held several corporate positions with Hastings Entertainment (1990-1999), including marketing, advertising, operations, and human resources. Hinckley has over 20 years of retail and business experience. He is a graduate of Utah State and holds a bachelor’s degree in political science and a master’s degree in human resource management.
</Bio>
        <URL>@Shane_Hinckley</URL>
		<Sessions>18</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>20</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Jankowich</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>John</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Trademarks and Licensing</Title>
        <Institution>Cracker Barrel</Institution>
        <Bio>John Jankowich has been a buyer for Cracker Barrel Old Country Store, Inc. for nearly ten years. He has more than 26 years of retail buying experience at a variety of retailers, including Caldor Department Stores, Staples, and Duckwall-Alco Stores. Jankowich is a 1988 graduate of The Pennsylvania State University with a degree in Telecommunications.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
		<Sessions>19</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>21</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Kaufman</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Lauren</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Trademarks and Licensing</Title>
        <Institution>WGSN</Institution>
        <Bio>Lauren Kaufman is the director of Strategic Services for WGSN and is the driving force behind WGSN’s consulting division in the Americas. A strategic and innovative thinker with a keen insight for qualitative analysis and an eye for design, she leads the Strategic Services team in managing the consulting business for both WGSN and Homebuildlife. Kaufman employs market research and future forecasting to identify consumer shifts, develop marketing and retail strategies, and provide business solutions for current and prospective clients. She has delivered insights to key senior management teams from Revlon, HP, Gap, Kimberly Clark, Colomer, Unilever, Disney, and Lululemon among others. Before joining WGSN in 2007, Kaufman honed her marketing acumen working at Macy’s, in addition to developing her account management skills with two full service advertising agencies. She is a native New Yorker and graduate of Colgate University.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
		<Sessions>20</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>22</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Kull</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Scott</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Trademarks and Licensing</Title>
        <Institution>Texas Christian University</Institution>
        <Bio>Scott Kull currently serves as the Associate Athletic Director for External Operations at Texas Christian University. He has also worked in the athletics departments of several other nationally recognized universities including Florida State, Ohio State  and Georgia Tech. Scott earned his bachelor’s degree in Business and Organizational Communications from Otterbein College, where he played football and was a member of the track &amp; field team. He furthered his education by earning a master’s degree in Sport Management from The Ohio State University. His passion for athletics has inspired both his career and his personal life, as he has participated in two Ironman (70.3) events with in the past year. In his position as the Associate Athletics Director, Scott is the sport administrator for nine of Texas Christian University’s athletic teams and supervises a staff of 40 that includes coaches as well as marketing, media relations, the ticket office, and spirit groups.</Bio>
        <URL>@TCU_Athletics</URL>
		<Sessions>21</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>23</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Lange</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Roland</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Trademark Licensing</Title>
        <Institution>YouTube/Google</Institution>
        <Bio>Since May 2012, Roland Lange has been the Partner Manager in the Sports Partnerships group at YouTube/Google, heading up content development and strategy for high school and college sports, along with the NBA. Prior to YouTube, he had been Major Accounts Lead in support of the Google Books, eBooks and Books on Play programs, responsible for creating Book Search Partnerships with top publishers and libraries in North America, India and South Africa. With over ten years of trade book publishing experience, Lange started with Google in September 2005 having left a sales position with Farrar, Straus &amp; Giroux.  He got his full-time start in book publishing with Penguin USA and has also worked for Perseus and Harcourt Trade. He was also the Vice President of Sales with the start-up Jungle Media Group, publishers of two National Magazine Award nominated magazines, MBA Jungle and JD Jungle, and websites for business and law school students. Lange holds a B.S. from Cornell University.</Bio>
		<URL></URL>
        <Sessions>22</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>24</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Lewis</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Shaun</First_Name>
        <Title>Brand Manager</Title>
        <Institution>Levi Strauss Inc.</Institution>
        <Bio>Shaun Lewis serves as global director of Public Relations and Collaborations for Levi Strauss’s Dockers division. In this role, he is responsible for developing the strategy for brand partnerships and managing collaboration programs from start-to-finish.  He also is responsible for developing Dockers’ annual public relations strategies and implementing strategic engagement programs through elements including media relations, social media, event promotion, and sponsorships. Prior to joining the Dockers’ team, Lewis served as account supervisor at LaForce + Stevens, where he developed and managed marketing initiatives and public relation strategies for multiple fashion brands. Lewis has also worked as an associate buyer for Charlotte Russe and as an associate designer for bebe. Lewis is a graduate of the Fashion Institute of Design &amp; Merchandising.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
		<Sessions>23</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
	<Record>
        <Speaker_Number>25</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Luker</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Dr. Richard</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Marketing</Title>
        <Institution>Luker on Trends</Institution>
        <Bio>Rich Luker, a social psychologist, has been studying American life for more than 25 years.  He is best known for his creation of the ESPN Sports Poll in 1994 which was the first ongoing intelligence tool for the American sports industry. His research on American community resulted in his first book Simple Community which was published in 2009. In 2004 he created and implemented a community engagement strategy with and for the more than 300 schools of NCAA Division II. Dr. Luker presented the seventh annual national “Division II Community Engagement Award of Excellence” to Southern Arkansas University in April of 2013 at the annual NCAA DII Workshop on Community Engagement held at the NCAA headquarters in Indianapolis. Dr. Luker earned his MA and Ph.D. at The University of Michigan and The Institute for Social Research. He has remained academically active with Northwestern University, The University of Oregon, The University of Michigan, and others.</Bio>
        <URL>@LukerOnTrends</URL>
		<Sessions>24</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
	<Record>
        <Speaker_Number>26</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Masherah</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Jason</First_Name>
        <Title>The University of Montana</Title>
        <Institution>Upper Deck Company</Institution>
        <Bio>Jason Masherah is the president of The Upper Deck Company, the world’s market share leader in sports trading cards and memorabilia. He is widely recognized as a leading strategist in the sports trading card industry with more than 20 years of experience. Prior to be named president, Masherah served as director of Sports Brands. He led several major brand campaigns, including the Yankee Stadium Legacy and Michael Jordan Legacy. Prior to joining Upper Deck, Masherah worked in corporate sponsorships with the Chicago Rush and in premium seating with the Cincinnati Bengals. He holds an MBA in Marketing from the Kelley School of Business at Indiana University as well as a B.A. in Marketing from the Eli Broad School of Business at Michigan State University.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
		<Sessions>25</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
	 <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>27</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Merriman</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Matt</First_Name>
        <Title>Associate Athletics Director</Title>
        <Institution>Columbia Sportswear</Institution>
        <Bio>Matt Merriman is the Product Licensing manager at Columbia Sportswear. In that capacity, Matt manages all aspects of Columbia’s licensing business, from developing new opportunities, to contract negotiation and drafting, to licensee and product management. In addition to the collegiate product line, Columbia’s licensed categories include: eyewear, timing, socks, hydration, and accessories, among others. Matt also manages the Pacific Trail brand, a fully owned Columbia subsidiary. Prior to joining Columbia, Matt was a practicing attorney at Frohnmayer, Deatherage et al in Southern Oregon. He holds a B.S. in Management Science from the University of California, San Diego as well as a J.D. and M.B.A. from the University of Oregon.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
		<Sessions>26</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>28</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Meza</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Randy</First_Name>
        <Title>Associate Athletics Director</Title>
        <Institution>Carhartt</Institution>
        <Bio>Randy Meza is a marketing director with 20 years expertise in brand marketing, advertising and media. In 2010, he launched Carhartt’s first national TV campaign in decades, which was short-listed for the Gold Lion award at Cannes. He has worked with talented teams to improve subsequent brand and product launches. Prior to Carhartt, he spent 15 years in brand management and field marketing with Colgate Palmolive, Coors Brewing Company and the Coca Cola Company. He began his career at Telemundo, the Spanish language TV network.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
		<Sessions>27</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
	 <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>29</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Mosler</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Tyler</First_Name>
        <Title>Creative Services Director</Title>
        <Institution>Dick's Sporting Goods</Institution>
        <Bio>Tyler Mosler is the NCAA &amp; High School Licensed buyer for Dick’s Sporting Goods. He has held a variety of buying positions at Dick’s since joining the retailer in 2002. During his tenure, Dick’s has grown from 110 stores to 487 stores plus 81 Galaxy Golf stores with plans for additional expansion in 2012. Before joining Dick’s, Mosler worked for Kaufmann’s Department Stores (a division of May Company) in various roles with increasing responsibility. Originally from Wapakoneta, Ohio, Mosler graduated from Miami University in 1999.</Bio>
		<URL></URL>
        <Sessions>28</Sessions>
    </Record>
	<Record>
        <Speaker_Number>30</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Parker</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Adam</First_Name>
        <Title>Creative Services Director</Title>
        <Institution>Brigham Young University</Institution>
        <Bio>Adam Parker has served as the manager of Licensing &amp; Trademarks at Brigham Young University since June 2008. He oversees the Office of Licensing &amp; Trademark Administration for BYU, BYU-Idaho, BYU-Hawaii, and the LDS Business College. Prior to BYU, Parker worked in marketing and promotions in the Athletic Departments of Boise State and LSU, respectively. Parker is a graduate of Boise State. He is the father of three kids, an avid football fan and sportsman, and loves Waffle House.</Bio>
        <URL>@parma26</URL>
		<Sessions>29</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>31</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Pasha</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Asim</First_Name>
        <Title>Creative Services Director</Title>
        <Institution>Sporting Kansas City</Institution>
        <Bio>With over 25 years of IT experience, Asim Pasha is the CO-CEO of Sporting Innovations and CIO /Chief Architect for Sporting Kansas City, Kansas City’s MLS soccer team. Pasha recently led the technical design and implementation at LIVESTRONG Sporting Park, which is Sporting Kansas City’s new soccer-specific stadium that is considered by many to be one of the most technologically advanced stadiums in the world.  His design covered 21 systems, including the first-ever deployment of CISCO High Density wireless, along with IPTV and broadcast over IP.   Prior to joining Sporting Kansas City, Pasha spent 13 years at Cerner Corporation, developing new architectures, strategies and solutions for the health care industry, including  Cerner Health Athlete, a player wellness tracking system used by both Major League Soccer (MLS) and the National Basketball Association (NBA). His current interests focus on leveraging advances in systems, networks and software platforms to progressively shift the innovation curve in the sports industry across the globe.</Bio>
        <URL>@SportingInnov</URL>
		<Sessions>30</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>32</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Pensy</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Ryan</First_Name>
        <Title>Creative Services Director</Title>
        <Institution>Silver Chalice</Institution>
        <Bio>Ryan Pensy recently joined Silver Chalice Ventures, which builds and operates a fast-growing portfolio of high-value digital media businesses in the fields of sports and entertainment. Prior to that, Pensy worked as Assistant Director of Athletics for Digital Media at Florida State, where he oversaw the official athletics website, Seminoles.com. He was responsible for identifying and overseeing the execution of the strategic new media plan for all intercollegiate athletics teams using original editorial and photographic content, live and on-demand audio/video-streaming and social networking to increase brand awareness, generate revenue and enhance website traffic/user activity. Pensy started his career as the Information Technology Manager for Florida State athletics. In 2005, he was named Florida State’s first Director of Digital Media. Pensy graduated from the University of Central Florida in 2002, where he earned a degree in Radio/TV with a minor in computer science. He later earned a master’s degree in sport administration from Florida State, during which time he served as a graduate assistant in the Seminole ticket and business offices.</Bio>
        <URL>@ryanpensy</URL>
		<Sessions>31</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
    <Speaker_Number>33</Speaker_Number>
    <Last_Name>Perlman</Last_Name>
    <First_Name>Doug</First_Name>
    <Title>Vice President of Sales &amp; Marketing</Title>
    <Institution>Sports Media Advisors</Institution>
    <Bio>Doug Perlman is the founder and CEO of Sports Media Advisors. SMA is a boutique advisory firm focused on the television and digital media industries as they relate to sports. SMA’s engagements are rooted in the firm’s media expertise and its ability to help entities navigate the complex sports landscape. Clients include a wide variety of domestic and international organizations including sports governing bodies, leagues, teams, media companies, TV networks, leading financial institutions, global consulting firms, and emerging digital businesses. Recent engagements include IMG, NASCAR, Little League, the USTA, the NFL, MLB, Hockey Canada, the PGA TOUR, the YES Network, Omnigon, Silver Chalice, AlixPartners, Red Bull, and Goldman Sachs. Before founding SMA, Perlman held senior leadership positions at the NHL and IMG. He is viewed as an industry leader who, among other things, has been named to the Sports Business Journal’s “Forty Under 40” and been recognized by The Sporting News as one of the “100 Most Powerful People in Sports.”</Bio>
    <URL></URL>
    <Sessions>32</Sessions>
</Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>33</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Peterson</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Dr. G.P. "Bud"</First_Name>
        <Title>Vice President of Sales &amp; Marketing</Title>
        <Institution>Georgia Institute of Technology</Institution>
        <Bio>Dr. G.P. “Bud” Peterson is the eleventh president of the Georgia Institute of Technology. In this capacity, he oversees a top-ten public research university with more than 21,000 students and more than $600 million in sponsored funding. Throughout his career, Dr. Peterson has played an active role in helping to establish the national education and research agendas, serving on numerous industry, government, and academic task forces and committees. A distinguished scientist, Dr. Peterson was selected in 2008 by President George W. Bush to serve on the National Science Board through 2014. The Board oversees the National Science Foundation (NSF) and advises the President and Congress on national policy related to science and engineering research and education. Dr. Peterson earned undergraduate degrees in Mechanical Engineering and Mathematics as well as a master’s degree in Engineering from Kansas State University. He earned his doctoral degree in Mechanical Engineering at Texas A&amp;M University.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
        <Sessions>32</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>34</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Prokup</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Tim</First_Name>
        <Title>Vice President of Sales &amp; Marketing</Title>
        <Institution>LiveU Ltd.</Institution>
        <Bio>Tim Prukop, Sports and New Media Director for LiveU Inc, is responsible for leading the effort to deliver LiveU’s patented bonded-cellular video uplink technology to the market. Prukop brings to LiveU over 20 years of experience in delivering cutting edge technologies into the sports and new media market. Before joining LiveU, Prukop was Vice President of Sales at Conviva and managed the North American sales team. Prukop held a similar position as Vice President of Sales for Demand Media and led the effort to introduce the Pluck social media platform that many publishers use today to interact with their fans. Before joining Demand Media, Prukop was responsible for sales and marketing at XOS Technologies, which provides the video editing systems that coaches use to analyze film and prepare their teams for games. During his tenure in sales, Prukop has leveraged his relationships in the sports industry to enable technology companies to successfully market their services in that industry.</Bio>
        <URL>@LiveU</URL>
        <Sessions>33</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>35</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Rogowski</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Ron</First_Name>
        <Title>Vice President of Sales &amp; Marketing</Title>
        <Institution>UPS</Institution>
        <Bio>As Vice President of Global Brand and Wponsorships, Ron Rogowski is responsible for overseeing the development and execution of the global brand and sponsorship strategy of UPS. His responsibilities also include managing key events that touch UPS’s internal and external customers. A native of Detroit, Rogowski joined UPS in 1985 and has held various positions in sales and marketing. Before joining the sponsorships and branding group in 2007, Rogowski worked on UPS’s go-to-market strategy for aligning the multiple sales organizations resulting from acquisitions the company made since going public in 1999. Prior to accepting the sales alignment assignment, he managed sales and marketing groups in New Jersey and Florida. Rogowski has also held various positions in corporate marketing including revenue management for strategic accounts and managing UPS’s small business strategy. His first management position with UPS was in a sales capacity. Rogowski earned his undergraduate degree from Wayne State University and a Master of Business Administration from the University of Detroit.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
        <Sessions>34</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>36</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Sabau</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Diana</First_Name>
        <Title>Vice President of Sales &amp; Marketing</Title>
        <Institution>The Ohio State University</Institution>
        <Bio>Currently an Associate Athletics Director of External Relations, Sabau provides oversight to its Creative Services, Fan Experience, Video Services, and Digital Media departments and serves as the departmental liaison for IMG and the Big Ten Network. Sabau’s daily responsibilities also include creating new revenue streams for the Athletics Department and tracking trends in technology for business advancement. Sabau began her professional career at Ohio State in 1993 as the Publications Coordinator before taking on the role of Publications Director in 1996. She served in this capacity until 2003, and her tenure encouraged brand consistency. As the Director of Branding and Creative Services, a position she accepted in 2003, Sabau continued to establish, educate, and maintain brand messaging throughout the Ohio State Department of Athletics. Sabau was promoted to Assistant Athletics Director, Creative Departments in 2007, overseeing the yearly goals, operations, and performances of the four creative areas: Branding and Public Relations, Website Development, Video Services and Creative Services.</Bio>
        <URL>@OhioStAthletics</URL>
        <Sessions>35</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>37</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Sabo</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>John</First_Name>
        <Title>Vice President of Sales &amp; Marketing</Title>
        <Institution>Fanatics</Institution>
        <Bio>John Sabo is senior vice president and general merchandise manager for Fanatics, the leading online retailer of officially licensed sports merchandise. Fanatics offers hundreds of thousands of officially licensed items via its Fanatics and FansEdge brands, as well as the largest selection of sports collectibles and memorabilia through Fanatics Mounted Memories. Fanatics also provides e-commerce sites for all the major professional sports leagues (NFL, MLB, NBA, NHL, NASCAR, PGA), major media brands (ESPN, NBC Sports, CBS Sports, FOX Sports) and over 200 collegiate and professional team properties. Prior to joining Fanatics, Sabo served as SVP Action Sports/Swimwear for Perry Ellis Inc. He also worked as general merchandise manager of Ron Jon Surf Shop and district merchandising manager and buyer at Federated Department Stores. Sabo is a graduate of the University of Florida.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
        <Sessions>36</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>38</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Sallerson</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Howard</First_Name>
        <Title>Vice President of Sales &amp; Marketing</Title>
        <Institution>Walmart</Institution>
        <Bio>Howard Sallerson joined Walmart in 2009 as the senior buyer of National Brands, Denim. He assumed his current responsibility of Team Sports buyer in January of 2010. Prior to joining Walmart, Sallerson was with Macy’s Atlanta for 21 years and prior to that he was with several divisions of Federated/Allied Dept. Stores. Sallerson has held many positions in his 30-year career, ranging from sales manager, assistant store manager to several buying positions in Men’s &amp; Kids Apparel. Sallerson earned his BS in Marketing from Florida Atlantic University in Boca Raton, Florida.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
        <Sessions>37</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>39</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Schiller</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Tony</First_Name>
        <Title>Vice President of Sales &amp; Marketing</Title>
        <Institution>Paragon Marketing Group LLC</Institution>
        <Bio>Tony Schiller has spent over 10 years creating sponsorship marketing partnerships in the entertainment industry working for professional basketball and hockey teams, two live entertainment venues, and a concert promoter. Schiller moved to the agency side in 1996 where he helped launch HALO Sports, the sports and entertainment division of HALO Industries. In 2001, HALO Sports was acquired by Paragon Marketing Group, of which Schiller is a founding partner.  He oversees client relationships for Paragon and is instrumental in developing and executing client strategies relative to sponsorship and promotional marketing. Paragon’s current clients include General Mills, Gatorade, ESPN, Lexus, Bayer Aspirin, Johnson &amp; Johnson, One A Day, PNC, Bank and Skull Candy. His team negotiates and manages a combined sponsorship, partnership, and promotions portfolio of over $150 million a year across sports, arts, entertainment, music, and media.</Bio>
        <URL>@HaloSport</URL>
        <Sessions>38</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>40</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Sobb</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Mike</First_Name>
        <Title>Vice President of Sales &amp; Marketing</Title>
        <Institution>Duke University</Institution>
        <Bio>A member of the Duke Athletics staff since 1988, Mike Sobb is an Associate Director of Athletics for External Affairs with daily oversight of marketing, promotions, group and season ticket sales, and corporate sponsorships. Sobb also has sport oversight responsibilities for men’s golf and serves as Chairman of the ACC Men’s Golf Tournament and ACC Marketing Directors Committees. Sobb is responsible for sponsorship sales, including game programs, Internet, signage, the Duke Radio Network, coach’s shows, and game day and event promotions. He is the primary contact for the Duke Radio Network and football and basketball television shows. Sobb also founded Duke’s Verizon Read With the Blue Devils program with the City of Durham school system. In addition, Sobb oversees the department’s car dealer program. As Promotions Director, Sobb’s former responsibilities included overseeing corporate sales, ticket marketing, and promotions. He coordinated the purchase, installation and implementation of the video board in Wade Stadium as well as new scoreboards and signage in Cameron Indoor, Koskinen, and Ambler Stadiums and at Williams Field.</Bio>
        <URL>@sobberatduke</URL>
        <Sessions>39</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>41</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Werner</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Bret</First_Name>
        <Title>Vice President of Sales &amp; Marketing</Title>
        <Institution>Catalyst PR</Institution>
        <Bio>Bret Werner joined Catalyst, an IMG Consulting Company, as Managing Director in 2006 and is spearheading the agency’s dynamic growth with global brands that include Subway Restaurants, Under Armour, and Dick’s Sporting Goods. During his tenure, the agency has experienced revenue growth every year while maintaining client and staff retention at over 90% on an annual basis. Prior to joining Catalyst, Werner spent 15 years at Taylor, becoming one of the youngest vice presidents in the company’s history. He has created a variety of marketing communications efforts to help distinguish consumer brands in a variety of industry categories, online, sports, health and packaged goods.  He helped develop consumer strategies for brands such as PowerAde, Microsoft’s Xbox, and ESPN.com. His work on behalf of MasterCard’s global sports sponsorships has taken him around the world, from the European Football Championships in England to the African Cup of Nations in South Africa, where he played an essential role in the development of global activation communication platforms.</Bio>
        <URL>@bret_werner</URL>
        <Sessions>40</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>42</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Wilder</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Laurie</First_Name>
        <Title>Vice President of Sales &amp; Marketing</Title>
        <Institution>Parker Executive Search</Institution>
        <Bio>Laurie Wilder is an Executive Vice President and Managing Director with Parker Executive Search. She joined the firm in 1999 as Associate and also has served as Principal, Vice President, and Senior Vice President. In her role, Wilder is responsible for business development, account management, and candidate development. She has been involved in all aspects of the search process, from conducting original research on candidates to meeting with educational institutions to determine their needs for an appropriate fit. She has successfully completed higher-education searches for university and community college presidents, vice presidents, deans, directors, athletic administration, and coaching professionals. She also has actively worked on middle- and senior-level searches in the sales, marketing, material management, logistics, human resources, general management, operations, manufacturing, construction, and finance disciplines. In addition to her duties at Parker Executive Search, Wilder has been an annual speaker at the Executive Leadership Institute for the National Association of Collegiate Women Athletics Administrators and the NCAA Champion Forum.</Bio>
        <URL></URL>
        <Sessions>41</Sessions>
    </Record>
    
</Records>




