<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<Records>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>5</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Arel</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Emilie</First_Name>
        <Title>Divisional Merchandise Manager</Title>
        <Institution>Old Navy</Institution>
        <Bio>Emilie Arel is the divisional merchandise manager of Brand Licensing and the Adult Non-Apparel &amp; Accessories divisions of Old Navy. She joined Old Navy in 2009 to lead the development and launch of the Licensing business for the brand, which operates over 1,000 stores in the U.S., Canada and Puerto Rico. Before joining Old Navy, Emilie was the head of Merchandising for the Women’s division for Gap Outlet. Emilie started her career in 2000 with Target Corporation, where she grew in successive roles in the company’s Women’s, Toys, and Strategy departments. Emilie lives in San Francisco and is pursuing a master’s degree at the Berkeley-Columbia Business School.</Bio>
        <Sessions>20</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>6</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Bartfield</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Jeremy</First_Name>
        <Title>Senior Merchant, New Business</Title>
        <Institution>Best Buy</Institution>
        <Bio>Jeremy Bartfield is the lead merchant and creator of the Best Buy Licensing Group.  The License Group oversees professional sports, college, novelty and pop culture licenses.  The License Group started in 2010 and has expanded to almost 900 Best Buy stores, and a licensed products and fan page site has been created on www.bestbuy.com.  In his 12th year at Best Buy, Jeremy has held various positions in the company and was a key contributor in the Napster acquisition and the rollout of Best Buy’s Musical Instruments Stores.  Prior to Best Buy, Jeremy worked for Target Corporation in the soft lines area. Originally from Boston, Jeremy is a graduate of Indiana University.</Bio>
        <Sessions>20</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>10</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Blackmon</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Jennifer</First_Name>
        <Title>Trademark Management &amp; Licensing</Title>
        <Institution>Auburn University</Institution>
        <Bio>Jennifer has worked in the Auburn University Trademark Management &amp; Licensing office of Auburn University for nearly 10 years.  Her responsibilities include coordinating retail and promotional initiatives, product category management, communication with licensees and assisting with strategic planning.  Before joining Auburn University, Jennifer worked for The Collegiate Licensing Company for eight years, where she directed licensing efforts for CLC’s conference and bowl properties, the NCAA, and special programs.  Jennifer holds a Bachelor of Science degree in Marketing from Auburn University.</Bio>
        <Sessions>21</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>54</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Bozich</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Joe</First_Name>
        <Title>Founder, Chairman, and CEO</Title>
        <Institution>Knights Apparel</Institution>
        <Bio>Joe Bozich is founder, chairman of the board, and CEO of Knights Apparel, one of the largest producers of college apparel. Joe is also the creator of the Alta Gracia brand, collegiate licensed apparel produced in the Dominan Republican in a factory paying a living wage.  Joe has extensive manufacturing, sourcing, marketing, and operations experience. He began his career as vice president of sales and marketing with Gold’s Gym and quickly advanced to the position of president of the clothing division. A graduate of Vanderbilt University with a B.S. in Mathematics, Joe was the 1985 NCAA National Bodybuilding champion and served as a spokesperson for Weider Enterprises, Gold’s Gym, the IFBB, and Mattel Corporation. He was named Ernst &amp; Young’s 2005 Entrepreneur of the Year for the Illinois Region. Huffington Post named Joe its “Ultimate Game Changer in Style” for 2010 for his Alta Gracia program.</Bio>
        <Sessions>44</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>24</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Chervany</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Todd</First_Name>
        <Title>Merchant Lead, New Business</Title>
        <Institution>Best Buy</Institution>
        <Bio>Todd Chervany has been with Best Buy for nearly 12 years in a number of positions in merchandising and business development. As the merchant lead for Best Buy’s New Business Customer Solutions Group, Todd and his team guide the company’s efforts to expand into new product categories, both in store and online.  In addition to licensed products, key categories include transportation, health and fitness, and home &amp; energy management.  Prior to joining Best Buy, Todd spent five years in the Leadership Development Program at American Express Financial Advisors.  He holds a BA in Government from Dartmouth College and an MBA from the University of Minnesota.</Bio>
        <Sessions>20</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>50</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Dyste</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Matt</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Marketing and Brand Management</Title>
        <Institution>University of Oregon</Institution>
        <Bio>Matt Dyste is the director of marketing and brand management at the University of Oregon. With expertise in marketing and licensing, Matt began and has grown the marketing and trademark licensing programs at the University significantly during his 20-year tenure. A past president of the International Collegiate Licensing Association, Matt enjoys speaking with and lecturing students, working with businesses seeking to work with the University, and spreading news of the great educational opportunities and game changing research being done at the University of Oregon.</Bio>
        <Sessions>4,42</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>15</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Eden</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Brett</First_Name>
        <Title>Licensing &amp; Marketing Director, Auxiliary Services</Title>
        <Institution>University of Utah</Institution>
        <Bio>Brett Eden is the director of Licensing &amp; Marketing for Auxiliary Services at the University of Utah.  He oversees the University’s licensing &amp; trademark program, as well as the marketing needs of seven other campus departments ranging from Print and Mail Services to Student Apartments to Commuter Services.  Brett has created many successful programs to grow the Utah licensing program, including the development of a licensed clothing line called the Boiling Point and licensed motorcycles, snow boards, skate boards, and long boards. Entering his fourth year at Utah, Brett came from local rival BYU, where he was the licensing manager for six years and also served in the Athletic Marketing office.   Brett currently serves as a board member for International Collegiate Licensing Association (ICLA).</Bio>
        <Sessions>28</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>8</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Goodenow</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Nikki</First_Name>
        <Title>Trademark Licensing Coordinator</Title>
        <Institution>West Virginia University</Institution>
        <Bio>Nikki Goodenow is completing her first year as the Trademark Licensing Coordinator at West Virginia University. She is responsible for generating revenue through sales of quality, licensed merchandise while protecting WVU’s name and indicia in the marketplace and beyond. A Rochester, N.Y., native, Goodenow previously spent nine seasons as an assistant women's soccer coach at West Virginia, helping the Mountaineers win a Big East championship and reach the NCAA Elite Eight. She also spent one season with adidas as the assistant license property manager in Notre Dame, Indiana.</Bio>
        <Sessions>21</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>4</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Hancock</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Bill</First_Name>
        <Title>Executive Director</Title>
        <Institution>Bowl Championship Series</Institution>
        <Bio>Bill Hancock is executive director of the Bowl Championship Series (BCS), where he oversees all operations, including licensing. Prior to joining the BCS, Bill served as the first full time director of the NCAA's Division I Men's Basketball Championship, a position he held for 13 years. For 11 years, he served on the staff of the Big Eight Conference, first as media relations director and then as assistant commissioner in charge of championships and marketing. A 1972 journalism graduate of The University of Oklahoma, Bill worked in the University's athletics department as assistant sports information director before serving as editor of his family’s daily newspaper, the Hobart Democrat-Chief. Bill has served on the United States Olympic Committee staff at nine Olympic games and two Pan American games and was inducted into the College Sports Information Directors Hall of Fame in 2005.
            
            In 2001, after the tragic death of his son in the crash of an airplane carrying members of the Oklahoma State University men's basketball team, he spent 35 days riding from Huntington Beach, California, to Tybee Island, Georgia. His memoir about the transcontinental bicycle journey, "Riding With the Blue Moth," has been among the top-selling sports books since it was released in October 2005.
        </Bio>
        <Sessions>17</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>2</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Hays</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Renata</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Licensing</Title>
        <Institution>The University of Oklahoma</Institution>
        <Bio>Renata Hays graduated summa cum laude in 2006 from The University of Oklahoma, where she double majored in Marketing and Public Relations.  In August 2006, Renata accepted one of six positions in the National Football League’s first-ever Blue Chip rotational program, where she served six-month stints in four departments: Fan Strategy; International in Frankfurt, Germany; Sponsorship; and Innovation.  At the completion of the two-year program, Renata assumed a permanent position in the NFL’s Sponsorship group, where she served as the day-to-day contact for league sponsors such as Bank of America, Bridgestone, FedEx and Visa.  She was also selected as one of 15 members of the NFL’s Diversity Council and served on the committee to recommend improvements to the NFL’s Bill Walsh Minority Coaching Fellowship. Renata returned to Oklahoma in 2009 to become the director of Licensing. Renata is responsible for protecting and promoting the University's reputation and image by ensuring the proper usage of its name, trademarks and other intellectual property, and managing OU’s $3.5 million licensing business.</Bio>
        <Sessions>8,29</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>7</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Hickley</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Shane</First_Name>
        <Title>Assistant Vice President of Business Development</Title>
        <Institution>Texas A&amp;M University</Institution>
        <Bio>Shane Hinckley is the assistant vice president of business development at Texas A&amp;M University, where he is responsible for the supervision of new and existing business opportunities with the University.  In this role, Shane oversees the on-campus bookstore, and the state license plate program as well as other business and marketing opportunities.
            He also directs the Texas A&amp;M licensing program, which administers the use of the University’s name, marks, and still and moving images with internal and external partners.  Prior to his joining Texas A&amp;M, Shane worked as the director of marketing &amp; licensing for auxiliary services at the University of Utah. He also held several corporate positions with Hastings Entertainment (1990-1999), including marketing, advertising, operations, and human resources. Shane has over 20 years of retail and business experience. He is a graduate of Utah State and holds a bachelor's degree in political science and a master's degree in human resource management. 
        </Bio>
        <Sessions>21</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>57</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Holihan</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Michael</First_Name>
        <Title>Owner</Title>
        <Institution>Holihan Law</Institution>
        <Bio>Michael Holihan is the owner of Holihan Law, Intellectual Property Protection, a law firm in Maitland, Florida that specializes in antitrust and trade, regulation, intellectual property, and litigation. He has represented many the world’s top brands in the protection of intellectual property rights. Michael has been a member, officer, and on the board of directors of the International Anti-Counterfeiting Coalition (IACC). Originally from Grosse Pointe, Michigan, he is a graduate of Spring Hill College and earned his juris doctor from Dickinson School of Law at Penn State.</Bio>
        <Sessions>43</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>20</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Langford</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Curtis</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Official Rings</Title>
        <Institution>Balfour</Institution>
        <Bio>Curt Langford joined Balfour in 2000 from Texas Tech University, where in 1998 he was instrumental in establishing what has become one of the most successful official ring stories in the country. With an eleven-year history in alumni programming, Curt has assisted many universities with the process of ring design, comprehensive program development and hosting of ring ceremonies. In this specialized role unique to Balfour, Curt works with partner institutions throughout the country to help implement official ring growth strategies and spearheads the Balfour Official Ring Workshops that take place in Austin and regionally that have drawn more than 250 attendees representing 76 colleges and universities to date. </Bio>
        <Sessions>32</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>53</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Lochbaum</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Derek</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Trademarks and Licensing</Title>
        <Institution>University of North Carolina</Institution>
        <Bio>Derek joined The University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill’s administration in August 2004. As the Director of Trademarks and Licensing, Derek’s current responsibilities include the overall direction and day-to-day management of the University's licensing program. Prior to his current position, Derek was the manager of Trademark Licensing The Pennsylvania State University, where he was presented the 2004 International Collegiate Licensing Association’s (ICLA) Synergy Award for the licensing program of the year. Past professional positions include the director of Tourism for Lycoming County (PA), home to the Little League World Series, academic advisor at Georgia State University, and event coordinator for ProServ, Inc. Derek is a graduate of Penn State and holds a master’s degree from Georgia State University. He is a member of the ICLA Board of Directors, serving as its President in 2009-10. </Bio>
        <Sessions>44</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>13</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Ludwig</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Marty</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Trademarks and Licensing</Title>
        <Institution>University of Cincinnati</Institution>
        <Bio>As the director of Trademarks and Licensing at the University of Cincinnati, Marty is responsible managing all internal and external relationships regarding the commercial use of the university’s name, identifying marks and images, and ensuring the university receives the appropriate commercial value for their use. He is also responsible for actively enforcing the university’s rights in marks and images against their unauthorized use, to protect and promote the goodwill and reputation of the university that they represent. Marty is a member of the University’s branding committee, Campus Services management team and executive marketing team, and the marketing committee for the university based healthcare system (UC Health). Marty is an active member of ICLA, serving as its third vice president on the Board of Directors. Marty has also coordinated a BIG EAST conference licensing director’s network to share information and enhance licensing programs within the conference. Marty has a BS in Finance and has over seven years of experience in the financial services industry managing assets for high net worth clients prior to joining the University of Cincinnati. </Bio>
        <Sessions></Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>12</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Malone</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Marsha</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Trademark Licensing</Title>
        <Institution>West Virginia University</Institution>
        <Bio>Marsha Malone is the director of Trademark Licensing at West Virginia University, where she ensures the department is compliant with state and federal laws, university standards, and policies and regulations, while advancing the university's retail presence and licensing program through marketing and public relations strategies. A WVU graduate, Marsha has worked in WVU trademark licensing since 1997.  She was promoted to director in 2008 and currently serves on the University's branding committee and on the Higher Education Opportunity Act (HEOA) Copyright Compliance committee.</Bio>
        <Sessions>28</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>16</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>McDonald</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Diane</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Social Media &amp; Marketing Programs </Title>
        <Institution>Texas A&amp;M University</Institution>
        <Bio>Diane C. McDonald is the director of Social Media &amp; Marketing Programs at Texas A&amp;M University. Since 2006, she has helped establish Texas A&amp;M as a national leader in social media and mobile marketing by launching one of the first 16 iTunes U sites in the nation, starting and growing the University’s official Facebook page to over 250,000 fan likes, rolling out the first suite of mobile apps for a public university and championing student-development of the third university Foursquare program in the nation. Her work has been featured in publications and websites such as Campus Technology, University Business, The Chronicle of Higher Education, Inside Higher Ed, and she has presented at more than 10 national conferences. She holds an MBA with a concentration in Management from the University of Arkansas. Prior to becoming an Aggie, Diane was the interim assistant vice president for Academic Affairs at Austin Peay State University in Clarksville, Tennessee. She has also held positions at John Brown University and Rheem Manufacturing, Inc.</Bio>
        <Sessions>29</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>19</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Miller</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Brandon</First_Name>
        <Title>Brand Manager</Title>
        <Institution>The Upper Deck Company</Institution>
        <Bio>Brandon Miller is the collegiate sports and Marvel entertainment brand manager for The Upper Deck Company, the world’s leader in sports trading cards and memorabilia.  He has over 10 years of experience in the sports and entertainment industry including the front office at the San Diego Padres and multiple sports agencies. Brandon holds a master’s degree from The George Washington University School of Business as well as a B.A. in Business Management from the Eller College of Business at The University of Arizona.</Bio>
        <Sessions>30</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>59</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Oldfield</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Melody</First_Name>
        <Title>Director of Marketing</Title>
        <Institution>Oregon State University</Institution>
        <Bio>Melody Oldfield has over twenty years of marketing and communications experience. She has been at Oregon State University since 1999 and is the University’s director of Marketing. At OSU, she recently launched a new integrated marketing communications plan for the university, a new brand identity system, and an image campaign called “Powered by Orange.” She has managed the University’s Trademark Licensing Program for six years. Prior to joining Oregon State, Melody spent eight years with Wachovia Bank in Atlanta in the Community Relations department assisting with the 1996 Olympic Games volunteer program and client promotions. Early in her career, Melody worked in account management in an Atlanta-based advertising agency. She holds a B.A. in Speech Communications from the University of North Carolina at Wilmington.</Bio>
        <Sessions>28</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>18</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Palmer</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Erika</First_Name>
        <Title>The University of Montana</Title>
        <Institution>The University of Montana</Institution>
        <Bio>Erika has been employed by The University of Montana since August 2001, beginning as a student employee.  She took on the role of Licensing Director at The University of Montana in September 2008 and serves as the liaison and University representative to approximately 280 licensees and the Collegiate Licensing Company.  Erika also serves as the assistant to UM’s Executive Vice President, Jim Foley. She has also been involved in the University’s award winning marketing campaign, which launched in the spring of 2006. Erika currently serves on the University’s Marketing Committee and the University’s Athletic Marketing Committee.  She is also involved with the Missoula Downtown Association, and a member of the Grizzly Scholarship Association. Erika is a graduate of The University of Montana, with a Bachelor’s Degree in Business Administration.  </Bio>
        <Sessions>29</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>56</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Rabinowitz</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Jeff</First_Name>
        <Title></Title>
        <Institution>Mounted Memories</Institution>
        <Bio>Growing up an avid sports fan, Jeff found his calling as a 20-year veteran in the sports collectible industry. During this time, he has been instrumental in helping grow the collectibles business while working with hundreds of athletes across all sports. One of his major accomplishments was spearheading the e-commerce initiative for the company during the Internet’s infancy. In addition, Jeff has sought out new avenues of distribution and tried to broaden the scope of the collectibles industry to a new audience. Jeff is a graduate of Florida State University.</Bio>
        <Sessions>31</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>21</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Rafael</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Russell</First_Name>
        <Title>Vice President of Business Development</Title>
        <Institution>Mounted Memories</Institution>
        <Bio>Russell Rafael is vice president of Business Development for Mounted Memories. He has more than thirty years experience in the licensed products, sports memorabilia, and collectibles industry including sales, licensing, show promotion, player relations, and manufacturing. He currently manages the collegiate business for Mounted Memories.</Bio>
        <Sessions>31</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>9</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Schlafer</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Jason</First_Name>
        <Title>Associate Athletics Director</Title>
        <Institution>University of Kentucky</Institution>
        <Bio>Jason Schlafer is in his 12th year with Kentucky and currently serves as Associate Athletics Director.  Jason oversees the marketing and licensing efforts for the entire athletics department, including his responsibilities for the marketing and branding portfolio of the Kentucky football and men’s basketball teams, both among the most nationally recognized programs. In addition to supervising a full-time staff and coordinating the season ticket sales and branding campaigns for the athletics department, Jason works to promote the Kentucky brand through its strategic trademark licensing program.  Under his leadership, Kentucky has experienced year-over-year growth in each of his 12 years managing the trademark portfolio. The Freeport, Ill., native and his wife, Michelle, have three sons, Wyatt (5) and Gabe (2) and EJ (9 mo).  The couple founded the Star Thrower Fund in 2008, a charitable fund devoted to improving the lives of orphans around the globe. </Bio>
        <Sessions>21</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>3</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Stevenson</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Scott</First_Name>
        <Title>Creative Services Director</Title>
        <Institution>UC Davis</Institution>
        <Bio>Scott Stevenson is the Creative Services director for UC Davis Athletics. In addition to managing all aspects of publication production (i.e., design, budget, proofing, printing), he also coordinates Athletics information for the various websites and other media outlets. He is also one of the technical advisory persons for Athletics and was instrumental in UC Davis’s bid to move up to the NCAA Division I level. In 2008 Scott was given the managerial responsibility of the Aggie Pride Outlet (APO). The APO is online at www.aggieprideoutlet.com and is open on football home contests as well as other selected home sporting events. As the Trademark Licensing manager at UC Davis, Scott provides administration and graphics/analytical oversight of the campus trademark licensing program. As a result of his work in trademark licensing 2009-10 was the University’s highest royalty producing year. Scott is a member of the International Collegiate Licensing Association (ICLA), Council for Advancement and Support of Education (CASE), and The University &amp; College Designers Association (UCDA). Prior his positions at UC Davis, He was the Production Manager/Art Director for Informant Communications Group, which published four monthly computer publications.</Bio>
        <Sessions>8,42</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>58</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>Swallow</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Brian</First_Name>
        <Title>Vice President of Sales &amp; Marketing</Title>
        <Institution>TeamFanShop, Inc.</Institution>
        <Bio>Brian Swallow is vice president of Sales &amp; Marketing for TeamFanShop, Inc.  He helped start Football Fanatics' Internet retail business in 2000. In 2004, Brian launched a business-to-business subsidiary called TeamFanShop, which powers official online stores for Division I athletic programs. Brian oversees all marketing aspects of the company, including new and existing business development, website design and usability, and social media.  Brian earned his B.S. in Marketing from the University of North Florida and is based in Jacksonville, Florida.</Bio>
        <Sessions>20</Sessions>
    </Record>
    <Record>
        <Speaker_Number>22</Speaker_Number>
        <Last_Name>VanBrimmer</Last_Name>
        <First_Name>Rick</First_Name>
        <Title>Director, Trademark &amp; Licensing Services</Title>
        <Institution>The Ohio State University</Institution>
        <Bio>Rick Van Brimmer has served as director of Trademark &amp; Licensing Services since 1999, and first joined the program in 1990. Rick is responsible for the strategic brand management of Ohio State’s commercial and entrepreneurial endeavors.  His innovations include licensing the first collegiate-themed restaurant (The Buckeye Hall of Fame Café); creation of the Ohio State Treasury of Fine Art licensing program to showcase the University’s extensive special collection library holdings; and the creation of the Healing Journey for Children licensing program that licenses children’s artwork for commercial products that help support the university’s James Cancer Clinic and Solave Research Center. Ohio State’s international trademark licensing program has been one of the top revenue-producing collegiate programs over the last 10 years, amassing nearly $70M in royalty revenues over that time, providing a myriad of support for student scholarship and programming to the Ohio State campus. Rick currently serves on the Board of Directors for the International Licensing Merchandisers’ Association (LIMA) and is a two time past president of the Association of Collegiate Licensing Administrators (ACLA).  He was given the International Collegiate Licensing Administrators’ Distinguished Service Award in 2005, and entered the ICLA Hall of Fame in 2011. He began his career in athletic communications, having served in the Sports Information offices at both the University of Mississippi (1983-85) and Ohio State (1985-90). Rick received both his undergraduate and master’s degrees from Ohio State.</Bio>
        <Sessions>44</Sessions>
    </Record>
</Records>




