<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<Records>

<Record>
      <Date>2013-05-14</Date>
      <Session_Name>Registration Opens</Session_Name>
      <Time>11:00 AM</Time>
	  <Room>Marquis Level, Imperial Registration</Room>
      <Description></Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>19</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
  <Record>
      <Date>2013-05-14</Date>
      <Session_Name>Welcome/Opening Remarks</Session_Name>
      <Time>2:30 PM – 2:45 PM</Time>
      <Room>Marquis Ballroom A/B</Room>
      <Description>Roger Vandersnick, SVP, Chief Sales &amp; Marketing Officer  - IMG College</Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>20</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
  <Record>
      <Date>2013-05-14</Date>
      <Session_Name>Industry Overview: The College Brand</Session_Name>
      <Time>2:45 PM – 3:15 PM</Time>
      <Room>Marquis Ballroom A/B</Room>
      <Description>173 million college fans and growing! Accompanying the explosion of the college fan base, large sponsors investing in collegiate marketing have rising expectations of service levels, exclusive access, and meaningful points of engagement. How do we better connect the most passionate fan base in sports to college brands in unique ways?;Roger VanDerSnick, Chief Sales and Marketing Officer - IMG College
      </Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>21</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
  <Record>
      <Date>2013-05-14</Date>
      <Session_Name>Break</Session_Name>
      <Time>3:15 PM - 3:45 PM</Time>
      <Room>Partner Symposium Lounge</Room>
      <Description>N/A</Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>21</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
  <Record>
      <Date>2013-05-14</Date>
      <Session_Name>Trending Now: New Media Opportunities</Session_Name>
      <Time>3:45 PM – 4:45 PM</Time>
      <Room>Marquis Ballroom A/B</Room>
      <Description>The evolving new media landscape is rife with opportunity…and opportunities for confusion. How can a college, university, or conference produce, distribute, and monetize unique content when live event rights may be owned by national and regional TV networks?  Learn what’s next from those inside and outside of college sports.;Moderator: Doug Perlman, Chief Executive Officer - Sports Media Advisors;;Panelists:;» Matt Carstens, General Manager - ACC Digital Network;» Ryan Pensy, Director, Senior Director of Products – Silver Chalice;» Tim Prukop, Sports and New Media - LiveU Ltd.
      </Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>22</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
  <Record>
      <Date>2013-05-14</Date>
      <Session_Name>Board Buses for the Opening Night Reception Sponsored by Logo</Session_Name>
      <Time>6:00 PM – 6:30 PM</Time>
      <Room>Marquis Ballroom A/B</Room>
      <Description>Join us for dinner at STATS on restaurant row in the heart of the Marietta/Luckie District for an evening of food, fellowship and fun. Busses will shuttle back to the hotel throughout the event.</Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>22</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
  <Record>
      <Date>2013-05-15</Date>
      <Session_Name>Registration Opens</Session_Name>
      <Time>7:00 AM </Time>
      <Room>Marquis Level, Imperial Registration</Room>
      <Description></Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>23</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
  <Record>
      <Date>2013-05-15</Date>
      <Session_Name>Breakfast</Session_Name>
      <Time>7:30 AM – 8:30 AM</Time>
      <Room>Imperial Ballroom</Room>
      <Description>N/A</Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>24</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
  <Record>
      <Date>2013-05-15</Date>
      <Session_Name>Ticketing and Seating Solutions for Building Fan and Revenue Bases</Session_Name>
      <Time>8:30 AM - 9:30 AM</Time>
	  <Room>Marquis Ballroom A/B</Room>
      <Description>There is ever-increasing pressure to deliver revenue through a variety of creative opportunities. We’ll learn from IMG Learfield Ticket Solutions and IMG Seating Solutions – two divisions that have strategically sourced new revenue streams while helping schools to better serve and expand their fan bases.;Moderator: Mark Dyer, Chief Innovation Officer-IMG College;;Panelists:;» Scott Carr, Senior Associate Athletic Director, External Affairs - Auburn University;;» Chris Ferris, Associate Athletic Director, External Relations - The University of Pittsburgh;;» Craig Bauman, Assistant Athletic Director, Ticket Manager - Oklahoma State University;;» Mike Sobb, Associate Athletic Director, External Affairs - Duke University;;»» Eric Brandt, Concessions and Game Day Hospitality – The University of Oregon
      </Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>25</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
  <Record>
      <Date>2013-05-15</Date>
      <Session_Name>Trending Now: In Venue Connectivity </Session_Name>
      <Time>9:30 AM – 10:15 AM</Time>
	  <Room>Marquis Ballroom A/B</Room>
      <Description>Today’s fans demand “always-on” access to unique content, social media, and all things digital. Who are the game changers and what is next?;Moderator: Doug Perlman, Chief Executive Officer - Sports Media Advisors;;Panelists:;» Scott Kull, Associate Athletic Director, External Affairs - Texas Christian University;;» Michael Alford, Senior Associate Athletic Director, Administration &amp; Development - The University of Oklahoma;;» Asim Pasha, Co-Chief Executive Officer - Sporting Innovations;CIO/Chief Architect - Sporting KC
      </Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>26</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Date>2013-05-15</Date>
        <Session_Name>Break</Session_Name>
        <Time>10:15 AM - 10:45 AM</Time>
        <Room></Room>
        <Description></Description>
        <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
        <Session_Number>26</Session_Number>
    </Record>
    
  <Record>
      <Date>2013-05-15</Date>
      <Session_Name>Path to Personal Growth: The Road to becoming an AD</Session_Name>
      <Time>10:45 AM - 11:45 AM</Time>
	  <Room>Marquis Ballroom A/B</Room>
      <Description>Amid increasing performance pressures, greater public scrutiny, and a myriad of options in outsourcing, how does one pursue his or her passion and become an athletic director?  Learn the desired characteristics and how this process works.;Moderator: Dutch Baughman, Executive Director - D-1A Athletic Directors Association;;Panelists:;» Dr. Michael F. Adams, President - The University of Georgia;;» Laurie Wilder, Executive Vice President and Managing Director - Parker Executive Search with Parker &amp; Associates;;» Dr. G. P. “Bud” Peterson, President - Georgia Institute of Technology
      </Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>27</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
  <Record>
      <Date>2013-05-15</Date>
      <Session_Name>Luncheon and Keynote Speaker Delivered by UPS</Session_Name>
      <Time>12:00 PM – 1:45 PM</Time>
      <Room>Imperial Ballroom</Room>
      <Description>Welcome and Comments: Ben C Sutton, Jr., President - IMG College, and Ron Rogowski, Vice President Global Brand &amp;Sponsorships - UPS;;Keynote Speaker: Dr. Richard Luker, social psychologist, founder of Luker on Trends and the ESPN Sports Poll, and author of “Living Simple Community” and “Building Simple Community”
      </Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>28</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
  <Record>
    
      <Date>2013-05-15</Date>
      <Session_Name>Sponsor Spending Patterns: Why College?</Session_Name>
      <Time>2:00 PM - 3:00 PM</Time>
      <Room>Marquis Ballroom A/B</Room>
      <Description>As the popularity of intercollegiate athletics continues to increase, so does corporate spending in college sports. These industry leaders discuss their strategic sponsorship priorities, investment plans and performance expectations, along with the challenges and opportunities topping their priority list.;Moderator: Bonnie Bernstein, Vice President, Content and Brand Development/Primary On-Air Host – Campus Insiders;;Panelists:;» Sharon Byers, Senior Vice President, Sports and Entertainment Marketing Partnerships – The Coca-Cola Company;;» Tony Schiller, Executive Vice President - Paragon Marketing Group, LLC;;» Ron Rogowski, Vice President, Global Brand &amp; Sponsorships - UPS
      </Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>29</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
  <Record>
      <Date>2013-05-15</Date>
      <Session_Name>Break</Session_Name>
      <Time>3:00 PM - 3:30 PM</Time>
      <Room></Room>
      <Description></Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>30</Session_Number>
  </Record>
  
  <Record>
      <Date>2013-05-15</Date>
      <Session_Name>Trending Now: Social Media Savvy</Session_Name>
      <Time>3:30 PM - 4:30 PM</Time>
      <Room>Marquis Ballroom A/B</Room>
      <Description>Twitter, Facebook, Instagram,  Foursquare, Pinterest, apps, and more!  In this rapidly-changing space, everyone is trying to stay ahead of the curve.  What are the hot trends, evolving demographics, and best practices to follow?  Learn from the leaders in creating and monetizing unique content.;Moderator: Ken Greer, Chief Marketing Officer – Augeo + Greer Marketing Agency;;Panelists:;» Bret Werner, Managing Director - Catalyst PR;» Brian Foley, Director, Sales &amp; Business Development Global Sports- Mass Relevance;» Roland Lange, Partner, Manager Sports Partnerships - YouTube
      </Description>
      <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
      <Session_Number>31</Session_Number>
  </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Date>2013-05-15</Date>
        <Session_Name>Trending Now: Creating VIP Programs that Impact the Bottom Line</Session_Name>
        <Time>4:30 PM - 5:30 PM</Time>
        <Room>Marquis Ballroom A/B</Room>
        <Description>The most passionate college fans want the unique access and experiences “everyone else” can’t buy.  Our experts will share best practices of game-day VIP experiential programs and beyond, which cement fan relationships while driving dollars to the bottom line.;;Moderator: Andrew Giangola, Vice President, Strategic Communications - IMG College;;Panelists:;;» Ohio State/Urban Meyer Coaches Show:;;» Ray DeWeese, General Manager - Ohio State IMG Sports Marketing.;;» Diana Sabau, Senior Associate Athletic Director, Strategic Communications – The Ohio State University;;» Kansas Special Touches:;;» Jason Booker, General Manager - Jayhawk IMG Sports Marketing;;» Jen Allee, Assistant Athletic Director, Marketing and Fan Experience - The University of Kansas;;» Court of Dreams &amp; Private Practices:;;» AJ Machosky, General Manager - St. John’s and Big East IMG Sports Marketing.
        </Description>
        <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
        <Session_Number>31</Session_Number>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Date>2013-05-15</Date>
        <Session_Name>Board Buses for Wild Wednesday Night</Session_Name>
        <Time>6:00 PM – 6:30 PM</Time>
        <Room></Room>
        <Description>Join us for dinner at Zoo Atlanta for a fun evening where the wild things are.</Description>
        <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
        <Session_Number>31</Session_Number>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Date>2013-05-16</Date>
        <Session_Name>Breakfast &amp; Registration Opens</Session_Name>
        <Time>7:30 AM</Time>
        <Room>Imperial Ballroom</Room>
        <Description></Description>
        <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
        <Session_Number>31</Session_Number>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Date>2013-05-16</Date>
        <Session_Name>Promotions that Fire Up Passionate Fans</Session_Name>
        <Time>9:00 AM - 9:30 AM</Time>
        <Room>Marquis Ballroom A/B</Room>
        <Description>Strategic planning and a creative use of intellectual property can result in unique experiences that excite fans and sponsors alike. Curated from the archives of IMG College, these promotional best practices drive fan engagement, are cost effective, and easy to execute.David Geren, Vice President, Sponsor and University Services - IMG College
        </Description>
        <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
        <Session_Number>31</Session_Number>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Date>2013-05-16</Date>
        <Session_Name>Trending Now: Intellectual Property Trailblazers</Session_Name>
        <Time>9:30 AM - 10:00 AM</Time>
        <Room>Marquis Ballroom A/B</Room>
        <Description>The intelligent and creative use of school marks can be a powerful way to build school brands, meet sponsor business objectives, and drive incremental revenue.  Learn how to incorporate the unique aspects of college into corporate messaging.;Roger VanDerSnick, Chief Sales and Marketing Officer - IMG College
        </Description>
        <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
        <Session_Number>31</Session_Number>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Date>2013-05-16</Date>
        <Session_Name>Closing Comments</Session_Name>
        <Time>10:00 AM – 10:15 AM</Time>
        <Room>Marquis Ballroom A/B</Room>
        <Description>Roger VanDerSnick, Chief Sales and Marketing Officer - IMG College
        </Description>
        <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
        <Session_Number>31</Session_Number>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Date>2013-05-16</Date>
        <Session_Name>Learn More: IMG Seating Solutions and IMG Learfield Ticket Solutions</Session_Name>
        <Time>10:00 AM - 11:30 AM</Time>
        <Room>Room: M103</Room>
        <Description>Optional Breakout</Description>
        <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
        <Session_Number>31</Session_Number>
    </Record>
    
    <Record>
        <Date>2013-05-16</Date>
        <Session_Name>IMG College Office Tours</Session_Name>
        <Time>11:30 AM – 2:30 PM</Time>
        <Room></Room>
        <Description>Tour 1:;;11:15 AM  Load bus - International Level Motor Lobby;11:30 AM  Leave Marriott Marquis;11:45 AM  Arrive at 1075 Peachtree;12:15 PM  Depart for Marriott;;Tour 2:;;12:15 PM  Load bus - International Level Motor Lobby;12:30 PM  Leave Marriott;12:45 PM  Arrive at 1075 Peachtree;01:15 PM  Depart for Marriott;;Tour 3:;;01:15 PM  Load bus - International Level Motor Lobby;01:30 PM  Leave Marriott;01:45 PM  Arrive at 1075 Peachtree;02:15 PM  Depart for Marriott
        </Description>
        <Speakers>N/A</Speakers>
        <Session_Number>31</Session_Number>
    </Record>
    
</Records>